Guide to the Goodwin J. (Goodwin Jess) Knight Papers, 1896-1988 (inclusive), 1946-1970 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series 9. Memorabilia and Miscellany
  - Portrait - TIME cover w/daughters1955, May 30, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193, Folder 23)
Peavey, Hollister M. - mayor, Huntington Park 38-249
Peckham, I. M. - SU/PAD 8-60; 12-76; 17-106; 25-146; 38-249
Penaat, William H. 17-106; 25-146; 27-164; 33-213; 38-249; 78-718
Pepperdine, George 22-136
Peterson, Leonard S. - mayor, Santa Maria 88-858
Pettijohn, L. R. - mayor, Hanford 17-106; 28-178; 38-249
Peyser, Jefferson E. (see also: SF Wine Inst.) 17-106; 28-178; 38-249
Phelps, Winfield 15-98
Phi Alpha Delta 8-60
Phillips, Herbert
Phillips, John (1887-) USHR 26-149 (re Acheson, Yorty et al); 38-249; 44-277; 79-727; 89-859; 99-958; 104-1013
Phillips, Patrick Henry (see also:Am. Legion/All-Am./Mem. Day) 17-106; 22-136; 38-249; 44-277; 78-718; 92-901; 105-1028; 112-1114
Pibulsonggram, P. Field Marshal - PM Thailand (to) 94-916
Piergue, Ralph 83-750
Pike, James A. - Bishop of Ca. 115-1152
Pinkley, Virgil - ed. LA Mirror 85-791; 109-1077A; 112-1116
Pitman, Paul M. UCSJ 12-76
Podesta, Jack - florist 119-1190
Porter, Carley V. (1906-) CA 38-249; 44-277
Post, A. Alan - Legislative auditor 38-249
Potter, David M. Babe - cousin 93-911
Poulson, Norris - mayor LA/USHR (1895-) 8-60; 28-178; 33-213; 38-249; 44-277; 85-800; 90-872; 100-965
Power, Domer F. - CA 105-1028
Powers, Harold J. Butch -(1900-) CS/Lt. Gov. Ca. 8-60; 12-76; 17-106; 22-136; 25-146; 38-249; 44-277; 112-1113, 112-1113
Pray, Russell N. 4-34; 17-106; 33-213; 78-718
Price, R. Fred (1890-) CA 12-76; 17-106; 33-213; 38-249
Pro America (see also: Cochran, J. L.) 8-60; 12-76; 25-146; 28-178
Pyle, Howard (1906-) Gov. Ariz. 33-213; 87-836; 94-916; 96-942; 109-1071A
Quinn, Irwin T. (1890?-) CS 3-15; 8-60; 78-719
Quinn, James H. (1902-) (see also: Ca. Bd. of Equalization) 8-60; 17-106; 22-136; 38-249
Quinn, William F. (1919-) Gov. Hawaii 113-1129 113-1129
Rall, Wayne - mayor Clovis 25-147
Randau, Clem - Chicago Sun 8-60; 12-77; 33-214; 39-250; 78-720
Rankin, John W. - SU 3-16; 8-60
Rapf, Harry - MPI 3-16
Rayburn, SAM (100-962)
Raycraft, Joseph - L/J 8-60; 12-77; 33-214; 44-277; 78-720
Reagan 121-1200
Republican State Central Committee (Carlson and Shattuck) (see also: Rep. Pty.) 8-60; 28-178
Reuther, Walter P. - pres. CIO 95-925
Reynolds and Painter - law firm 74-649
Reynolds, Thomas - LP 8-60; 12-77; 17-106; 28-178; 33-214; 39-250; 44-278; 74-650; 74-657; 74-695; 78-720; 79-727; 83-750; 85-796; 86-823; 91-900; 92-901; 100-964; 107-1044; 117-1168.
Rice, Glenn - MAHS/TV producer 12-77
Rich, W.P. - CS 12-77; 28-178; 33-214; 39-250
Richards, Richard - CS 107-1044
Rickenbacker, Edward V. -Eastern Air Lines 103-1005; 116-1165
Rickey, John - restaurateur 39-250
Riesner 121-1099
Rinn, Robert - mayor, Lodi 17-106
Rishell, Clifford E. - mayor of Oakland 25-147; 28-178; 44-278
Robbins, Charles W. - CA 17-106; 45-284
Robbins, Wesley 78-720
Roberts, Dennis J. - Gov. R.I. 113-1123
Robie, Wendell T. 17-106; 25-147; 39-250 (see also: Auburn 49er Assn.)
Robinson, C. Ray - pres. Golden Gate Fields 103-1006
Robinson, Edgar E. - prof. history SU 39-253 re: retirement
Robinson, Edward G. - E 39-250 re: son's trial
Robinson, Elmer E. - J/mayor SF 8-60; 27-165; 33-214; 39-250; 44-278; 78-720; 98-954; 99-955; 102-985
Rockefeller, Nelson
Rogers, John M. - Elephant-Eagle Mines 74-650; 74-658; 74-695; 78-720
Rogers, Roy 115-1152
Rogers, Will Jr. - E/pol. cand. 3-16 (see also: American Legion)
Rogers, William P. - Dep. Atty. Gen. 100-964; 119-1190
Rolph, James III 12-77; 78-720; 102-991
Romulo, Gen. Carlos P. - Philippines amb. to UN 101-968
Roosevelt, James - Dem. nominee for Gov. 22-137; 27-166; 39-250
Rosellini, Albert D. - Gov. Wash. 100-964; 110-1088; 115-1150; 117-1164; 119-1190
Rosen, David V. - Knowland campaign dir. 3-16; 12-77; 39-250
Rosenberg, Nate 8-60; 12-77; 22-137; 33-214; 44-279
Rosenblatt, John - mayor, Omaha 93-915
Ross, Kenneth A. Jr. - CA 89-866
Rumford, Wm. Byron - CA 33-214; 39-250
Russell, Charles H. - Gov. Nevada 95-926; 104-1010; 107-1046; 119-1190; 55-383
Salsman, Byrl R. - CS/J 8-61; 12-78; 17-108; 39-251
Salsman, Eleanor L. (see also: P.A. Rep. Women's Club) 3-17; m. by R. G. Alderman 8-26-49)
Samish, Artie - lobbyist 12-78; 14-94; 27-167; 39-251
San Diego Rep. Women 3-17; 8-61 (see also: Johnson, L. Bence, R.)
San Francisco Co. Rep. Central Committee 8-61 (see also: H. Hanley)
San Joaquin Co. Rep. Central Committee 8-61 (see also: B. Crittendon)
Sanders, Everett L. (Calif. State Athletic Commission) 3-17; 8-61; 12-78; 17-108; 22-138; 25-147; 33-215; 39-251; 44-279
Sapiro, Aaron - L 8-61; 12-78; 17-108; 25-147; 28-178; 39-251; 85-804; 90-875
Schary, Dore - MPI 22-138; 39-251; 90-874
Schenk, Joseph - MPI 8-61; 22-138; 25-147; 33-215; 39-251
Schmidt, George R. 8-61 (re: Ruben Schmidt's death)
Schrade, Jack - CA 103-1004; 103-1006; 110-1089; 114-1132; 116-1162; 55-383
Scoggins, Verne 78-721
Scott, C. Beecher 8-61; 17-108; 22-138 (re: Voorhis and Douglas)
Scott, Joseph - L 4-34; 8-61; 12-78; 17-108; 22-138; 33-215; 39-251; 44-279; 78-721; 92-902; 114-1132
Scudder, Herbert B. - USHR 22-138; 39-251
Sequeria, F. - secy. to Gen. Consul India 105-1022; m. 120-1193
Shanley, Bernard M. - secy. to President 107-1050
Shattuck, Edward S. - RSCC 4-34; 12-77; 12-78; 17-108; 25-147; 27-168; 28-178; 33-215; 39-251; 100-965; 106-1033; 107-1047; 108-1053; 108-1054; 114-1133; 120-1193 (see also: Western Airlines)
Sheldon, George E. - cand. Lt. Gov. 1938 44-279
Shellenberger, George (see also: Merchants...Assn.) 17-108; 22-138; 39-251; 44-279; 45-284
Shelley, John F. - USHR 3-17; 28-178; 39-251; 44-279; 108-1053; 120-1193
Shenk, John W. - J 39-251
Sherwin, Marvin - CA 33-215; 39-251 (re: Stanford YRs)
Shivers, Alan - Gov. Texas 87-837; 89-871
Short, Alan - CS 111-1094
Short, Dewey - USHR 101-970
Silliman, James W. - CA 8-61; 39-251
Simmons, Rosemary Bernheim - niece 44-279
Simms, John F. - Gov. N.M. 101-971; 103-1005
Simon, Bob 85-803; 108-1053
Simon, Jack 121-1199
Simpson, Milward L. - Gov. Wyo. 55-383; 108-1053; 110-1089; 118-1173; 119-1190
Simpson, Roy - Supt. Public Instruction 27-169; 28-178; 39-251
Simpson, Sid - USHR 119-1184
Sinclair, John 78-721
Skouras, Spyros P. - MPI 91-895; 118-1173; 120-1193
Slater, Herbert W. - CS 3-17; 8-61
Small, M. F. - adm. asst. Kuchel 114-1130
Smith, A. Ellis 17-108; 39-251 (on verso handwritten note by GJK re:Hawaii)
Smith, C. Arnholt - financier 12-79; 39-251; 44-279; 119-1187
Smith, Elmo - Gov. Oregon 55-383
Smith, H. Allen - CA/USHR 39-251; 90-874; 99-957
Smith, L. K. - mayor Monterey 17-108
Smith, Paul - SF Chronicle 8-61; 39-251
Smith, Paul - SF Chronicle 8-61; 39-251
Smuin, John LeRoy 92-902 re: Arvilla's father's death (Sacto.) 2-14-55
Smylie, Robert E. - Gov. Idaho 55-383; 93-915; 96-946; 105-1023; 107-1051; 108-1053
Snyder, Rixford K. - SU 100-964
Son, Charles W. 78-721
Sons of the American Revolution 8-61
Southern Calif. Rep. Women 8-61 (see also: Parshalle, E.)
Southern Crossing Committee 44-279
Spaeth, Carl B. - SU 108-1067
Spangler, Harrison W. 78-721
Spangler, Ray - P 108-1053
Sparling, Capt. Maurice C. - J 8-61; 22-138; 33-216; 39-252; 83-750; 91-900; 92-901; 102-992
Spaulding, G. A. - CS/CA 17-109; 39-252
Speidel, Merritt C. - P 44-279
Spellman, Francis Cardinal 92-902 tls
Spence, Homer R. - J 8-61; 33-216; 39-252; 44-279
Spiering, Frank P. 3-17; 8-61; 78-721 (see also: Vallejo Rep. Club)
Spivak, Lawrence E. - Meet the Press 101-970
Spreckles Co. vs. All Persons 9-67 (see also: Calrk, H. W.)
Sproul, Robert Gordon - UC 8-61; 12-79 (see also: Cal., U. of)
Standard Oil Co. of Calif. 8-61; 17-109; 22-138; 39-252
Stanford Alumni Assn. 3-17; 17-109
Stanford University 8-61; 12-79; 17-109; 22-138; 39-252; 107-1046; 113-1125; 119-1187
Stanley, Thomas B. - Gov. of Va. 111-1095
Stassen, Harold C. 55-383; 78-721; 108-1053
Stanton, Frank - pres. CBS 108-1053
Stearns, Newton A. 46-300; 46-305; 47-317; 99-958
Stengel, Casey 94-916
Sterling, J. E. Wallace - SU 119-1187
Stewart, A. I. - CA 39-252; 44-279; 114-1132
Stolz, Louis P. - SU 92-901; 114-1132
Storke, Charles A. - P 17-108
Storke, T. M. - CS/P/SU 3-17; 12-79; 17-109 re: Fred Houser; 22-138; 39-252; 84-768; 94-920; 102-991; 108-1053, 108-1053
Stratton, William G. - Gov. Ill. 55-383; 103-1006; 115-1147; 117-1164; 119-1190
Straus, Richard 89-859
Strehlow, Arthur F. 8-61; 12-79; 28-178; 39-252; 78-721; 91-893; 85-804; 101-971 (see also: Calif. Rep. Assly.)
Sullivan, Edward E. - E 33-216; 39-252
Sullivan, Mark - Pacific Tel. and Tel. 120-1193
Summerfield, Arthur E. - US Postmaster General 101-967
Sutherland, George - J 74-696
Sutro, Adolph 101-970; 109-1071A (see also: Purple Heart)
Sutton, Louis G. - CS 12-79; 17-109; 39-252; 93-906
Sweigert, William T. - exec. secy. Warren 3-17; 8-61; 39-252; 78-721
Swing, Ralph E. - CS 8-61; 12-79; 22-138; 28-178; 39-252
Sylva, Tillie - aunt 44-279
Synon, John - campaign strategist 22-138; 25-147; 28-178; 33-216; 39-252; 46-297; 86-821; 90-872; 91-900; 93-912; 101-970; 108-1053
Taft, Robert - USS, Pres. cand. 23-139; 27-170
Takasugi, Kanji - Consul of Japan 105-1025
Tannenbaum, David - mayor Beverly Hills 108-1057; 109-1077; 115-1154
Taylor, L. D. Babe - mayor Dunsmuir 25-148; 39-253; 44-279
Teague, Charles M. - USHR 99-958
Telluride Assn. 8-62 (see also: Johnson, E.)
Tenney, Jack B. - CS 3-18; 8-62; 12-79; 18-110; 28-178; 34-217; 39-253; 44-279; 78-722; 85-812; 89-867 (see also: AECS)
Thieriot, Charles deYoung - P 103-1004
Thomas, Vincent - CA 44-279; 108-1057; 111-1095
Thompson, John F. - CA 12-79; 34-217; 39-253; 44-279; 85-808; 87-837; 106-1043; 108-1058; 110-1088; 117-1167; 118-1174
Thomson, Vernon W. - Wisc. Atty. Gen. 101-973; 117-1164
Thornton, Dan - Gov. Colo. 23-139; 87-836
Thurman, Allen G. Scoop - CS 8-62; 12-79; 18-110; 34-217; 39-253 (see also: Grass Valley, 10-70)
Tibbett, Lawrence M. - E/MAHS 3-18
Tibbetts, Mary - P (see also: Woodland Record/ Yolo Co. Record) 12-79; 34-217; 39-253, 121-1199
Tickle, Edward H. - CS 3-18; 12-79; 18-110; 39-253; 44-279; 78-722
Tide Water Assn. Oil Co. 8-62; 39-253
Times-Mirror Bldg. Dedication 12-79
Timmerman, George Bell Jr. - Gov. S.C. 103-1004
Todd, Michael - adv. agency 45-283
Tognazzini, Roland - Union Sugar Co. 12-79; 18-110; 28-178; 39-253
Toll, Henry W. - Senator Colo. 87-836
Tomlinson, Stanley T. - CA 44-279
Town Meeting radio broadcast 8-62
Townsend, Viner 86-823
Tracy, Frank C. - YRs, Ca. 3-18
Tressider, Donald B. - SU 3-18
Trower, Stella - cousin 8-62
Truman, H. S. Library 44-279
Tunney, Gene 55-381; 103-1005; 114-1136
Tuso, Johnnie (re: Riverside cement dust control problem) 18-110; 23-139; 39-253
Ullrich, Paul G. (see also: Nevada Co. RCC) 3-18; 34-218; 40-254; 45-281; 78-723; 90-880,881
Underwood, Cecil H. - Gov. W. Va. 111-1095
Union Carbide and Carbon Corp. 91-893
Union Oil Co. 23-139; 45-281
United Spanish War Veterans 8-62
U.S. Naval School, Monterey 13-80
Vai, James -vintner 13-80; 18-111; 23-139; 34-218; 40-254; 45-281; 92-901; 103-1004,1006; 110-1089; 114-1139,1140; 116-1162; 120-1195
Vandervoort, Ray 8-62
VanLoben Sels, James F. 109-1071A
Van-Tets, William - Consul Gen. Netherlands 101-977
Vasey, Beach -legal secy. Warren (see also: Calif. - Gov.'s Office) 13-80; 40-254; 78-724
Vermillion, George M. - mayor Long Beach 95-934
Veterans of Foreign Wars 8-62; 13-80; 40-254
Villagran, Francisco - Consul Gen. Mexico, See also: Mexico) 8-62
von Dehn, Hyatt R. - pres. Hyatt House Hotels 101-968
von Kleinsmidt, Rufus B. - pres. USC 78-724
Von Zell, Harry - E 40-254
Walsh, Christy - PR 3-19; 4-34; 23-140; 34-219; 40-255; 45-281 (to T. Kuchel); 74-700
Ward, Clarence - CS 8-62; 23-140; 25-148; 40-255
Ward, Stuart R. - Commonwealth Club SF 8-62
Warner, Harry M. - MPI 40-255; 115-1153
Warner, Jack L. - MPI 114-1142
Warren, Earl - Gov. Ca. 3-19 re: Cherniss; 4-34; 8-62; 13-80; 27-171; 28-178; 34-219; 40-255; 108-1061 birthday; 119-1190
Waters, Laughlin E. - CA (see also: RSCC) 34-219; 40-255; 45-281; 90-885
Watkins, Charles A. 13-80 m. Stanwyck divorce case
Watson, Clyde A. - CS 8-62; 18-111; 23-140
Watson, Dean D. - Ca. Real Estate Com. 23-140; 40-255
Way, Arthur W. - CA 18-111; 23-140; 28-178; 40-255; 45-281
Weedman, Mrs. Charles S. Sr. 93-911; 104-1009; 108-1061
Weedman, Charles S. Jr. Mrs. (Carolyn Knight) 108-1061; 113-1125; 114-1146
Weinberger, Caspar W. Cap - CA/secy HEW 40-255; 45-284; 55-384; 93-906; 109-1071A
Welburn, Nelson Grady - American Legion 18-111
Wellborn, Olin III - chief counsel for Doheny/ADP 3-19
Wellington, Col. M. B. - Ca. State Bar Assn. 3-19
Werdel, Thomas H. - USHR 23-140; 34-219; 40-255
Western Airlines (see also: Shattuck, E.) 8-62
West-Sleeth, 74-676
Weybret, Fred 13-80; 40-255; 90-885; 92-902(Mrs.)
Whitaker and Baxter - Campaigns, Inc. 3-19; 8-62; 13-80; 18-111; 23-140; 25-148; 34-219; 40-255; 46-290, 294, 297, 299, 304, 305, 306; 47-317; 55-381, 383; 56-391, 392; 57-397A,B; 90-885; 91-900; 93-911; 97-946; 98-954, 955, 956; 99-957, 958; 100-960; 101-979; 102-985; 105-1032; 106-1034; 106-1043; 108-1061, 1062; 112-1118; 112-1119; 114-1142, 1143; 117-1167; 118-1174
White, Hugh - Gov. Miss. 89-871
White, K. J. M. - Consul Gen. GB 84-780
White, Lawrence J. - MAHS 3-19; 8-62
Whitehorn, Ethel Gillett - P Rep. Spokesman 3-19; 8-62; 13-91
Whitman, Ann C. - secy. to President 100-965
Whitney, John Hay - Am. amb. to London 119-1187
Wilbur, Ray Lyman - SU 74-700
Williams, G. Mennen - Gov. Mich. 101-979; 108-1061; 114-1142
Williams, J. Howard - CS 8-62; 18-111; 40-255; 45-281; 95-928; 112-1112; 120-1197
Williams, L. B. - re: Jewish campaigners 8-62
Williamson, Jessie Mrs. - see also: Whitehorn, E.
Willkie, Wendell T. - Pres. cand. 78-725
Wilson, C. E. - US Secy. Defense 107-1050
Wilson, Charles H. -CA 113-1122
Wilson, Geraldine - MAHS 3-19; 8-62
Wilson, Leonard - L 8-62
Wilson, Robert C. - USHR 40-255; 99-958
Winbigler, H. D. - see also: Stanford University
Winchell, Walter - columnist 34-219; 45-281
Winton, Gordon H. Jr. - CA 114-1143
Witter, Dean - Stock broker 103-1005
Wolfson, Burnett - J 93-911; 108-1061; 113-1126; 114-1142; 118-1174
Woman's Council Sacramento 8-62
Women in Govt. LA 8-62
Woodman, Frederick T. - mayor LA 3-19
Woolley, Roland Rich 3-19; 8-62 L
Wyatt, Jane - E 118-1174
Yorty, Samuel William - mayor LA 13-80; 40-256; 108-1064
Young, Truman R. - cand. USHR 3-19
Younger, Mrs. Evelle J. 29-191; 34-220; 45-281; 12-77; 89-868; 109-1071A,1077
Younger, J. Arthur - USHR 40-256; 99-958
Zanuck, Darryl F. - MPI 13-80; 34-220; 40-256
Zellerbach, Harold L. 83-750; 87-836; 94-916; 103-1004; 110-1089; 116-1162
Zellerbach, James David - amb. to Italy 119-1187; 55-382
Zimmerman, Fred R. - Wisc. Secy. State 23-140 re:IOOF
Zionist Organization of America 8-62